// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
  {
  numb: 1,
  question: "Who is the father of C language?",
  answer: "Dennis R",
  options: [
    "Steve Jobs",
    "Dennis R",
    "Raja Ram Mohan Roy",
    "Akhbar"
  ]
},
  {
  numb: 2,
  question: "which of the following s not C variable?",
  answer: "int $main",
  options: [ 
    " int $main",
    "Int number",
    "Float rate",
    "None of these"
  ]
},
  {
  numb: 3,
  question: "All keywords in C are in ____?",
  answer: "Lowercase letters",
  options: [
    "Lowercase letters",
    "Uppercase letters",
    "Camelcase letters",
    " All of these"
  ]
},
  {
  numb: 4,
  question: "Is C case sensitive?",
  answer: "Yes",
  options: [
    "Yes",
    "NO"
  ]
},
  {
  numb: 5,
  question: "What is short int in C?",
  answer: "Short & int",
  options: [
    "Short & int",
    "Integer",
    "Both A & B",
    "None of these"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 6,
  question: "When was C invented?",
  answer: "1972",
  options: [
    "1995",
    "1972",
    "1943",
    "1999"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 7,
  question: "What is C's extension?",
  answer: ".c",
  options: [
    ".sj",
    ".c",
    ".html",
    "None of these"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 8,
  question: "In how many ways can C be written by?",
  answer: "4",
  options: [
    "1",
    "2",
    "3",
    "4"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 9,
  question: "Which HTML tag used to declare internal C?",
  answer: "Style",
  options: [
    "Link",
    "Script",
    "Style",
    "None of these"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 10,
  question: "What is data-type in C?",
  answer: "Declaratio for variables",
  options: [
    "Declaration of variables",
    "List-style-type",
    "UL",
    "List"
  ]
},
// you can uncomment the below codes and make duplicate as more as you want to add question
// but remember you need to give the numb value serialize like 1,2,3,5,6,7,8,9.....

//   {
//   numb: 6,
//   question: "Your Question is Here",
//   answer: "Correct answer of the question is here",
//   options: [
//     "Option 1",
//     "option 2",
//     "option 3",
//     "option 4"
//   ]
// },
];